尼克森议员 我希望你知道
Congresswoman Nickerson, I just want you to know
空军一号
上午 10:21
我不会忘记国会的老朋友
that I won't forget my friends in Congress.
这些真好看
These are fabulous.
她的人说她想要杯子
Her people say she wants the mug.
你想留着这个杯子放... 小面包车里吗?
Would you like to keep the mugs for your... minivan?
你怎么知道我有面包车?
How did you know I have a minivan?
我猜的
Just a good guess.
我竞选国会议员之前是个家庭主妇 六个孩子
Before I ran for Congress, I was a stay-at-home mother of six.
是啊
Yeah.
如果小面包车到不了的地方
I tell you, if I could not
我一定去不了
get there in a minivan, then I wasn't going.
- 是啊 - 你明白的
- Right. - You know the drill.
我当然知道 是啊
Indeed I do, yeah.
我驾照过期好几年了
I mean, my license expired a few years ago,
不过我明白个大概
but I get the general idea.
那 佩妮 佩妮
So, Penny. Penny.
我们准备重批水陆两用战舰
We want to reauthorize the amphibious fighting boat
并且建在你的行政区里
and have them built in your district.
我刚才在外面看见个印着空军一号的毯子
I saw a blanket out front that said Air Force One on it.
还挺好看的
It looks really beautiful.
拿个咱们的礼品包
Let's get one of our care packages
然后装个毯子进去
and then we can throw one of those blankets in there.
- 还有那些抱枕? - 当然
- With the throw pillows? - Yeah.
所以 我能指望你的支持吗?
So what do you think? Can I count on your support?
某问题啦票票来啦
Okey-dokey, Annie Oakley.
Annie Oakley美国著名神枪手 三十步之外射穿纸票 之后门票上的洞眼被称为Annie Oakley 也代称各种票圈
你真是太贴心了
Bless your pea-picking heart.
你想从空军一号上打个电话吗?
Would you like to call someone from Air Force One?
- 总是能吓到别人 - 天呐
- That usually freaks people out. - My gosh.
我家唐纳德 他今天化疗
My Donald. He has chemo today.
太棒了
Fantastic.
让我再告诉你们一些赛琳娜·梅耶的事
Let me tell you something else about Selina Meyer,
瑞安竞选集会
新罕布什尔州 康科德
上午 10:24
我们贼一样的指挥官
our commander-in-thief.
快看第三排的咪咪
Check out the tits in the third row.
我能把它们当篮球运来运去
I could dribble those things like basketballs.
她搞砸了经济
She has destroyed the economy,
候选人乔纳·瑞安新罕布什尔竞选活动
搞砸了中东
made a mess of the Middle East,
毁了感恩节
she ruined Thanksgiving,
这只用了10个月
and that's all in just 10 months in office.
肯特说乔纳的支持率上升了五个百分点
Kent says Jonah's up another five points.
- 等等 什么? - 我们会在纳舒厄取胜
- Wait, what? - We're gonna win in Nashua.
我们还会在彼得伯勒 基恩 以及伯瑞特波罗
And we're gonna win in Peterborough and Keene
取胜 没错!
and Brattleboro, yeah!
我是乔纳·瑞安 而我...
My name is Jonah Ryan and I...
决不妥协!
Won't back down!
白宫新闻发布会
下午 1:01
- 麦克! 麦克! 麦克! - 吉姆 吉姆
- Mike! Mike! Mike! - Jim. Jim.
麦克 海军都不需要
Mike, the navy doesn't even
水陆两用战舰了
want the amphibious fighting boat anymore.
那把工厂建造在国会议员
Is it a coincidence that the plant
尼克森的行政区内是否只是个巧合呢?
that builds it is in Congresswoman Nickerson's district?
吉姆 如果我们国家的敌人
Jim, if our nation's enemies
投个球弹引发战争
decide to drop the puck on hostilities,
我们的海军和同盟国将会非常高兴
then our navy and our allies will be very glad
我们拥有足够的军事能力
we have the military capabilities we need.
- 投球弹? - 常用的曲棍球术语 唐娜
- Drop the puck? - Common hockey term. Donna.
麦克 关于总统女儿凯瑟琳的问题
Mike, question about the president's daughter Catherine.
- 传闻是真的吗... - 我刚刚听到信号了
- Is it true that... - I just heard the buzzer.
第三期到此结束
That is the end of the third period.
- 下次我们再见 - 麦克! 麦克!
- See you at the next face-off. - Mike! Mike!
有了尼克森的支持
You know, with Nickerson's support,
我们至少赢了75％的科罗拉多
that clinches Colorado for us four to three.
这个看着可不像圣诞老人
That doesn't look like Santa.
白宫官方庆祝排灯节[印度教节日]
The White House officially celebrates Diwali,
圣诞节 光明节[犹太教节日] 匡扎节[非裔美国人的节日]
Christmas, Hanukkah, Kwanzaa
- 还有圣纪节[伊斯兰教节日]… - 我知道
- and Mawlid al-Nabi... - I know.
先知穆罕默德所谓的生日
the alleged birth date of the prophet Muhammad.
好像挂几张穆罕默德的照片
Well, I suppose putting a
从来没伤害谁一样
few pictures up of Muhammad never hurt anyone.
女士 有很多记者对凯瑟琳感兴趣
Ma'am, I'm getting a lot of press interest about Catherine
- 关于她的状态 - 什么?
- and, you know, her condition. - What?
她只是个同性恋 麦克 她又不是狼人
She's a lesbian, Mike. She's not a werewolf.
不过两个都能解释她为什么从来不刮腿毛
Although either one would explain why she never shaves her legs.
- 还有什么事吗? - 是的
- Anything else? - Yeah.
《国会山》前50名性感员工名单出来了
"The Hill's" 50 Hottest Staffers list is out.
白宫最没用的
When does the White House's
新闻发言人名单什么出来?
most useless press secretary list come out?
我等不及看看今年的第一名是谁了
I can't wait to see who's number one this year.
- 我投麦克一票 - 我讨厌那个名单
- I voted for Mike. - I hate that thing.
每次都意味着整个月
Every year it means a month
一群饥渴的参议院助手偷瞄我胸部
of horny Senate aides looking down my blouse.
而且 他们的统计学不健全
Also, their methodology is unsound.
今年你好像不在名单里面啊 艾米
I don't think you're in it this year, Ame.
这不得了 艾米 问题解决了
There you go, Amy. Problem solved.
我勒个去 凯蒂·卡罗索居然排第17
Oh, my God, Candi Caruso ranked 17.
快看这图 不是吧 猜猜第21是谁
Look at this picture. No way, look who's 21.
- 是盖瑞 - 什么?
- Gary. - What?
那谁排22? 象人?
Who's 22? The Elephant Man?
出自美国传记电影《象人》主人公脑袋硕大无比 身体畸形酷似大象
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
嘿 21
Hey, 21.
去弄点洛神花茶 要不我就开了你
Rose hip tea, okay? Or I'm gonna 86 you.
俚语指开除 使某人消失
《信使报》刚刚宣布支持我们
Just got an endorsement from the "Courier."
汤姆·佩蒂的律师发来的邮件
The emails from Tom Petty's
简直跟洪水猛兽一样[音乐人 禁止乔纳用歌梗 S5E6]
lawyers keep on getting angrier and angrier.
《国会山最性感50名职员》怎么能没我?
How am I not on "The Hill's" 50 Hottest Staffers list this year?
今年? 这是最性感50名职员 乔纳
This year? It's the 50 Hottest Staffers, Jonah,
不是审判前最有可能玩自杀的50人排名
not the 50 people most likely to kill themselves before trial.
丹 现在我事业可是如日中天 直冲火星啊
I am on a career rocket ship to Mars right now, Dan,
不过我可不带马特·达蒙回来[2015电影《火星救援》]
except I'm gonna leave
因为那个傻逼竟然用自己的屎煮土豆
Matt Damon there because the guy made potatoes
跟未开化的动物没啥两样
in his own shit like a fucking animal.
性感排名这种榜 不上才好
The whole point of the 50 Hottest is not to be on it.
- 你排第26啊 伊根先生 - 是啊连续五年了
- You're number 26, Mr. Egan. - Yeah, five years in a row now.
正确用法是研究一下谁可以操
It's to use it to learn who to fuck.
- 谁? - 找个去年上榜 但今年落榜的妹子
- Who? - Find a woman who was on it last year, but not this year.
我种就是她给你操
I mean, that's like a "Make
- 还会顺便把晚饭钱结了 - 有用吗?
- her pay for dinner" Situation. - Does that work?
对于长得不像你这种
If you don't look like someone
旗杆顶上插坨黏泥巴的人 会有用的
melted Play-Doh all over a flagpole, it does.
你真是个屌爆了的竞选经理啊
Wow, you're a fantastic campaign manager.
知道就行 卧槽盖瑞都排21?
Yeah. Fucking Gary's number 21?
什么? 这简直是对性感排名
What? Well, that just makes
概念的极大讽刺
a mockery of the very idea of hot rankings.
其实也有点道理 他眼挺好看的
Well, it makes sense. He's got beautiful eyes.
- 他们来了 - 总统女士
- There they are. -  Madam President.
- 先生们好啊 - 小崽子们
- Hello, gentlemen. - Children.
好 我们直接切入正题 早点结束
All right, let's get to this. Let's make it quick.
罗杰 你来过一遍流程吧?
Roger, you want to walk us through the drill right now?
求你说得文明点?
And would you please, please try and keep it clean?
总统女士 明晚就是总统举办的年度节日派对
Madam President, tomorrow night is the president's annual
需要招待议员及其亲属
holiday party for congressional members and their families.
女士 届时得由你来开场
Ma'am, you'll need to make the initial approach.
本负责服务事宜
Ben will keep the offer straight.
肯特管账
Kent will keep a running tally.
汤姆 你就负责随时救火
Tom, you'll be in charge of putting out any fires.
一切掌控有序之后 就轮到我出场
And once you're all done with them, I'll move in
往国会众菊花里射爆
and squirt a half gallon of ropey jism
我乳白粘稠不可思议的精液
into their modeled congressional cornholes.
你开头说的那么好 结果还是...
Oh, you made it so far and then you just...
汤姆你有什么好补充的么?
Tom, do you have anything that you would like to add?
没了 罗杰把我关于精液方面的都提到了
No, Roger took my thing about ropey jism.
- 行吧 - 谢谢您 总统女士
- Right. - Thank you, Madam President.
- 那汤姆 我们是明晚见 没错吧? - 没错
- And I will see you tomorrow night, right, Tom? - Indeed, yes.
好
Okay.
怎么了?
What's up?
肮脏 简直是肮脏下流
Dirty. Just dirty and shady.
门 关上门
Door. Door.
怎么着?
So?
他妈的汤姆是想搞什么幺蛾子?
What the fuck is Tom up to?
他在韩国烧烤店跟珀赛尔碰面是要干嘛?
Why was he meeting with Purcell at a Korean barbecue place?
- 马伍德不是我们这边的 - 他在帮奥布莱恩?
- Marwood is the opposition. - You think Tom is helping O'Brien?
奥布莱恩能给他什么好处?
But what could O'Brien offer
能比过副总统的职位?
him that's better than the vice presidency?
其实什么都比副总统强
Literally anything.
汤姆想当财政部长来着
Oh! Tom wanted Secretary of the Treasury.
不过被我拒了 卧槽
I said no. Ah, fuck!
女士 你只需要继续拉票
Ma'am, you just have to keep nailing down those votes.
再拿下26票我们就赢了
All right? 26 votes and it's over.
好吧 伙计们 明天晚上都给我盯着点汤姆
Okay, guys, we got to keep an eye on Tom tomorrow night.
- 讲真 - 明白 女士
- Really. - Yes, ma'am.
- 有事吗? 我就是瞅瞅
- Yes? - I was just checking
是不是也有什么秘密会议在讨伐我
to see if there was another meeting about me.
今天没有
Not today.
下个问题请问瑞安先生
All right, the next question is for Mr. Ryan.
瑞安竞选总办公室
新罕布什尔州
下午 2:03
你支持提高债务上限吗?
Would you vote to raise the debt ceiling?
已故伟人莱昂纳尔·里奇曾说
Well, as the late, great Lionel Richie once said,
"这是怎样的滋味 在债务上限狂舞"
"Oh, what a feeling, I am dancing on the debt ceiling."
第一 莱昂纳尔·里奇 还没死呢
Okay, A, Lionel Richie is not dead,
第二 扯那个蛋有鬼用?
B, what the fuck does that even mean?
新罕布什尔喜欢我的段子
New Hampshire loves my zingers.
能有今天 全是靠我的个人魅力
It's my personality that has gotten us this far.
得了吧 那都是靠我才有现在这成绩的
No, I am the one who got us this far,
你这人形灌肠器
you sentient enema.
谢尔曼夫人 同样的问题 [模拟辩论 理查德饰谢尔曼夫人]
All right, Mrs. Sherman, same question.
我在此庄严宣誓 如没有预算补偿
I hereby solemnly promise to never vote
我绝不支持提高债务上限
to raise the debt ceiling without budgetary offsets.
天知道我每周都恪守日常开支预算
Lord knows I stick to my grocery budget every week.
简直是圣玛利亚抱着枕头摩擦自慰啊
Mother Mary dry humping a pillow.
这才是天赋
That is what I call natural talent.
- 你叫啥来着? - 朱迪·谢尔曼
- What was your name again? - Judy Sherman.
得了吧 理查德之所以胜出
Oh, come on, Richard's only winning because he gets to be
全在于他可以做老好人  但我要坚守本心
the easier person and I have to be me.
好吧 朱迪 扮演下乔纳
All right, Judy, pretend to be Jonah.
理查德根本不可能...
Richard's not gonna get the subtleties of being...
闭嘴 滚那边去!
Just shut the fuck up and move!
在财政职责方面
I'd have to agree with Mrs.
我赞同谢尔曼夫人的观点
Sherman here on fiscal responsibility.
事实上 老师 请允许我用这苹果展示一下
In fact, teacher, allow me to present you with this apple.
谢尔曼夫人为乔纳小学二年级老师 见上集
感受一下我的老二 我现在可是为你硬到炸了 先生
Feel my dick. I am rock-hard for you right now, mister.
别以为我在开玩笑 有种来试试
You think I'm kidding. Feel it.
- 卧槽 - 怎么了
- Shit. - What?
地方新闻电视台在直播集会
Local news stations are running footage from the rally.
- 你刚才说布拉特尔伯勒镇 - 那怎么了?
- You said Brattleboro. - So?
- 布拉特尔伯勒镇在佛蒙特 - 什么时候的事?
- So Brattleboro just happens to be in Vermont. - Since when?
当然 这里的城镇不过都是
Granted, every town up here is just
廊桥连起来的两坨脏兮兮的雪堆
two dirty piles of snow connected by a covered bridge,
但是看在耶稣的份上 乔纳 你在这长大的
but Jesus Christ, Jonah, you grew up here.
怎么会不知道这种破事?
How do you not know this shit?
我不知道啊
I don't know. Maybe I was
可能二年级的时候教这个
supposed to learn it in the second grade,
但是我的老师是个臭婆娘
but my teacher was a fucking bitch.
乔纳 注意你的语言
Jonah, watch your language.
看来艾瑞克森在这个活动里放置了眼线
Well, obviously Ericsson had trackers at the event.
- 理查德 我们有什么眼线监视这个寡妇么? - 没有
- Richard, who do we have tracking the widow? - Nobody.
那就滚出去然后买个照相机
Then go out there and buy
把她干的所有事都给录下来
a camera and videotape everything she does.
- 你想要普清的还是高清的? - 就去他妈的买个相机
- Do you want 4k or 1080p? - Just buy any fucking camera.
- 我这就去 - 我们俩得谈谈
- Okay, I'm going. - You and I have to talk.
如果你能少黑10%的话
If you were like 10% less black,
- 我能让你当总统 - 谢谢
- I could make you president. - Thank you.
白宫绿厅
下午 7:03
不用这个 不 不 拿出去
No. No. No. That's-- get it out.
我们说好的 普莱特议员的夫人设计的
We talked about this. The wife of Congressman Platt designed it.
她知道我不是古巴总统吗?
Does she know I'm not the president of Cuba?
你跟她说过吗? 你喷了古龙水?
Did you tell her that? Are you wearing cologne?
用了一点
A little.
闻起来跟鸟屎似的
Smells like birdseed.
- 嘿 妈妈 - 嘿 亲爱的
- Hi, Mom. - Hi, darling.
你好 马乔里 你看起来真...
Hi, Marjorie. Don't you look...
- 魁梧 - ...魁梧
- Strapping. - ...strapping.
- 谢谢您 女士 - 这两卷触手是怎么回事?
- Thank you, ma'am. - What's happening with these tentacles here?
你准备挪走它们吧 至少?
Are they gonna get put away or something?
我有个问题 我需要知道...
I have a question. I need to know how you...
你们俩准备怎么处理这个同性恋的事情
gals want to play the whole gay thing.
抱歉 我不知道...
I'm sorry, I don't know...
迈克最近接收到很多类似的问题
Mike has been getting a bunch of questions
还有采访要求之类的
and interview requests and, you know, et cetera, et cetera.
我不知道你要怎么处理这个
And I just don't know how you want to handle that.
你想像艾伦那样呢[艾伦秀主持人 公开同性恋]
Do you want to just play it like
还是像朱迪·福斯特那样呢?[好莱坞同性女演员]
Ellen or do you want to be more like Jodie Foster?
弄得神秘一点?
Do you want to play it more like a mystery?
我觉得我们还是比较期望
Uh, I think that we were kind of
能低调一些
hoping that we could keep things on the down-low.
你会讲英语吗 凯瑟琳?
Okay, can you just speak English, Catherine?
因为我实在不知道你在说什么鬼
'Cause I don't know what you're trying to say.
总统女士 请允许我说
Madam President, if it's all the same to you,
我们不太想把我们的私人生活政治化
I mean, we don't want our private life to be politicized.
好吧 我知道了 我对此表示尊敬
Okay. I get that. I respect that.
我们把它控制在姬达范围之外的
We'll keep it under the gaydar.
- 谢谢 - 那么 太好了 我会告诉迈克的
- Thank you. - So, great. I'll tell Mike.
国会招待舞会
白宫东厅
女士们先生们... - 拿着
Ladies and gentlemen... - Here, take it.
- ...美国总统 - 谢谢
- ...the President of the United States. - Thank you.
谢... 你能好好听着么?
Thank... would you listen to this?
谁不喜欢合唱团啊?
Who doesn't love a cappella, right?
就像魔术表演似的
It's like a magic trick
因为没有乐器
'cause there are no instruments, of course.
总统女士 汤姆·詹姆斯 八点钟方向
Madam President, Tom James, 8:00.
好的
Okay.
你指的是十一点方向么
You mean 11:00? Over there?
你真的不认表吗
Seriously, can you really not tell time?
抱歉 女士 我以为是接近了的意思
Sorry, ma'am, I just thought it meant close.
- 女士? - 干嘛?
- Ma'am? - Yes.
差不多都做好准备了
The fluffers have done their work.
群交狂欢该开始了
It's time for the orgy to begin.
好的早死早超生
Okay, let's get that done.
凯瑟琳 你把头发修理好了
Oh, look, Catherine. You fixed that there, didn't you?
- 是 - 但是后面看起来还是像老鼠窝
- Yeah. - Except it's still just a rat's nest in the back.
你得要去拉... 或者你能来帮帮她 马乔里
It needs to pull... maybe you can help her, Marjorie.
就把它拉到后面去就好 甜心
Just pull it back, sweetheart.
我的朋友们都来了
Oh, all my friends are here.
- 总统女士 您好 - 圣诞快乐
- Madam President, hello. - Merry Christmas.
- 感谢你邀请我们 - 你好 议员耶格
- Thank you so much for having us. - Hello, Congressman Jaeger.
- 这一定是耶格夫人? - 这不是他老婆
- And this must be Mrs. Jaeger? - That's not his wife.
- 好吧 - 这是我的手下之一 纳迪亚
- Okay. - This is one of my staffers, Nadia.
她是个妓女
She's a prostitute.
好吧 你想要拍张照
Well, would you like a
拿给家人朋友看吗?
picture for your friends and for your family?
- 好.. - 我们需要..
- Yes... - We've got a...
好样的 别
There we go. No.
我想祝你们圣诞快乐
And I want to wish you a merry Christmas.
并且我很期待你的支持
And I can count on your support,
- 你会支持我吧? - 百分之百 圣诞快乐
- can't I? - 100%. Merry Christmas.
- 太棒了 谢谢你 - 新年快乐 纳迪亚 我们走吧
- Wonderful, thank you. - And Happy New Year. Nadia, let's go.
这位是亚利桑那州的议员本斯
This is Congressman Baines from Arizona.
他是奥布莱恩那头的
He's solidly O'Brien.
让我们拍张照吧 走你
Oh, let's get a picture. There we go.
然后你差不多能走了 走吧
And you're out of here. You can go.
凯瑟琳二十三岁了 她又不是不能碰
Catherine's 23 years old. She's fair game.
这个新闻你就先放放 让她坐一会冷板凳
Maybe you ride the pine on this one for a period or two.
- 好吗? - 好的 我去跟别人说说
- Please? - All right, I'll talk to everyone.
- 我欠你一个人情 - 我指的是 我很不喜欢越线
- I owe you. - I mean, I'd hate to be offsides.
- 什么? - 你懂得 冰球啊
- What? - You know, hockey.
冰球 真是个好运动 谢谢
Hockey. Great sport. Thank you.
迈克 你是在跟一个冰球运动员约会么?
Mike, are you dating a hockey player by any chance?
你听到了冰球的术语?
You noticed the hockey references?
该死 我以为不会有人知道呢
Shit, I thought they were seamless.
听着 你不能说出去 但是我们的代孕妈妈已经怀孕了
Listen, you can't say a word, but our surrogate is pregnant
而且我在跟冰球联盟的人谈工作
and I've been talking to somebody in the NHL
我说不定能去那里当新闻发言人
about a job as director of communications.
所以不管如何 我都能离开这里了
So win or lose, I'm out of here.
好吧 让我先跟你说声再见好了
Well, let me get my good-byes out of the way now.
议员
Congressman, the president would
总统女士希望能和你在绿厅里谈一下
love to have a clutch with you in the Green Room.
- 当然啦 - 太棒了
- Oh, of course. - Great.
- 嘿 - 你好
- Hey. - Hi.
卡森城 内华达见过的
Carson City, Nevada.
巴迪·卡尔霍恩
Ah, Buddy Calhoun
竟然戴着一条不是线条纹的领带
in a tie that's not made out of string.
你是唯一一个威胁我会把我的蛋蛋磨碎
You're the only woman who's ever threatened
撒在一碗通心粉上的女人
to grate my balls over a bowl of spaghetti.
- 夜还长着呢 你慢慢磨 - 好的
- Night's still young. Knock yourself out. - Well, yeah.
白宫绿厅
总统夫人
Madam President, we are
我们想要在波兹曼建一个911纪念馆
looking to build a 9/11 memorial in Bozeman.
好极了
That sounds superb.
太难得了 因为 你懂的 永不遗忘
Wonderful, because, you know, never forget.
- 不错 - 永远铭记
- That's right. - Always remember.
但是你能确切的帮我回忆一下
But can you remind me exactly what happened
911那天波兹曼发生了什么?
in Bozeman on 9/11?
主要是为了我们的现场急救员
This is mainly focused on our first responders.
那真是太重要了
Oh, that's so important.
我们的现场急救员被发生在
Our first responders were terribly traumatized
纽约现场急救身上的事深深的创伤了
by what happened to the first responders in New York.
我懂了 那真是...
Yeah, I get that. That's, uh...
- 哇 - 那真是... 哇 本
- Wow. - That's... wow. Yeah, Ben.
我确信我们会为如此重要的事情
You know, I am sure there is a little something
找到可以做一点事情的地方 先生
we can find somewhere for such a great project, sir.
罗杰 你觉得呢?
Roger, what do you think?
我觉得我们可以把它塞进
Oh, I'm sure we can just slip it under the skirt
国土安全的裙子下面  给他们解释一下 威尔
of the Homeland Security budget. Tell him why, Will.
他们的预算比我的屁股还要胖还要娘气
The budget has a fatter, more womanly behind than myself.
打扰一下 你是盖瑞·沃尔什吗?
Excuse me. Aren't you Gary Walsh?
- 我干什么了? - 你必需过来见见我的女儿
- What did I do? - You've got to come meet my daughter.
她在《国会山》上读到你
She saw you in "The Hill."
她是单身 离婚了 有一个孩子
She's single, divorced, has a kid.
- 但是他是个小甜心 - 真棒
- But he's really a sweetheart. - Oh, how nice.
天呐 我感觉有人在耍他
God, I feel like somebody's playing a trick on him.
有人要给他的头上倒一桶猪血了
They're about to dump a bucket of pig's blood on his head.
白宫红厅
你过得怎么样 艾米?
You having a good time, Amy?
不敢相信
Can't believe how many
我因为那个性感名单得到了多少恭维
compliments I'm getting about the hot list.
这的人除了那个破烂性感名单
Don't people around here have anything better
不会说的别的吗?
to talk about than the stupid hot list?
- 艾米 想听我的建议吗?  - 绝对不想
- Amy, do you want some advice? - Definitely not.
别为了这部分的事儿担心过度
Listen, don't worry so much about what's up here, okay?
主要想想这里面是什么 如果你为此努力了
Worry about what's in here. And if you work at that,
我告诉你 你会重回性感名单的 艾米
I'm telling you, you're gonna be back on the hot list, Amy.
我不是说你会在前20
I'm not saying you're gonna be in the top 20,
- 但你绝对可以到40左右 - 谢谢
- but you would be a lock for, like, mid 40s. - Thank you.
看看他 他在笑
Look at him, he's smiling
就像他的屎闻起来是新鲜的菠萝味
like his shit's all pine-fresh smelling.
好吧
Oh, okay.
- 你在干嘛? - 什么?
- What are you doing? - What?
你在对着镜子孤芳自赏吗?
You're looking at yourself in the mirror?
- 你看起来不错 - 对
- You look wonderful. - Yeah.
总统女士
Madam President.
这位是俄勒冈州的康妮·达苯尼林
This is Connie DiBenedetto of Oregon.
她是同性恋核心会议主席
She's the chairman of the Gay and Lesbian Caucus.
事实上 她是同性恋核心会议唯一的成员
Actually, she's the only member of the Gay and Lesbian Caucus.
我想占用你一点点的时间
I'd like to take just a moment of your time
谈谈关于你的环境政策
to talk to you about your environmental policy.
好的 嗯哼
Oh, yes. Uh-huh.
- 我知道它是政治不正确的... - 这边
- I know it's politically risky... - Come this way.
...但是 你知道 二氧化碳税是唯一的出路
...but, you know, a carbon tax is the only way to go.
- 这是我女儿凯瑟琳 你们见过了吗? - 没
- Yeah, you've met my daughter Catherine? - No.
这位是她的特殊伙伴马乔里
And this is her special friend Marjorie.
我想来一起合一张影
I want to get a picture of all of us.
不 妈 我们不想照相
No, Mom, we don't want to take any photos.
当然 我们要的 我们超想要的
Sure, we do. We're dying to do that.
所以 就在这里吧
So, here we go right here.
让我们一起说女孩最大
Let's all say girl power.
- 女孩最大 - 女孩最大
- Girl power. - Girl power.
我真希望我够潮可以和你们呆在一起
Listen, I wish I was hip enough to hang here with you all,
- 但我要去处理一下... - 你真是个忙人
- but I've got to go deal with... - You're a busy girl.
- 告诉丽兹我爱她 -  我会的
- Tell Liz I love her. - Oh, I will.
- 好的好 再见 - 她会爱死这个的 再见
- Okay. Okay. Bye-bye. - She'll love that. Bye.
瑞安竞选总办公室
新罕布什尔州
下午 8:02
今晚我们有个保龄球馆的活动
Tonight we've got the bowling alley appearance
不能再失态了
and we can't have any more gaffes.
我有了! 我有了!
I got it! I got it!
那个寡妇看见我在拍她就生气了
The widow saw me filming her and she got mad.
她说了我一些真的很难听的话
She called me some truly awful things.
- 谢谢你 撒旦 - 可以翻盘了
- Oh, thank you, Satan. - I think this is a game changer.
感谢大家的到来
Thank you all so much for coming.
天呐 到手了 好料到手!
Oh, my God, I got it. I think I got it!
我好想知道发生了什么
You know, I think I see what happened there.
理查德 你是个好孩子
Richard, you good boy.
我去开它 但它已经开了 所以我是关了
I went to turn it on, but it was already on, so I turned it off.
然后我去关它
Then I went to turn it off,
但它已经关了 所以我把它打开了
but it already was off, so I turned it on.
理查德 枉我对你的期望啊
I had such plans for you, Richard.
巴克斯特议员 我绝对相信
Congressman Baxter, I completely believe you
你的这个男士房间的提议
about the whole men's room incident.
听起来就觉得貌似有道理
It sounded very plausible to me.
所以我也要祝你圣诞快乐
So I want to also wish you a merry Christmas.
- 十分感谢 - 这位是 保罗·格雷福斯 来自紫色州
- Thank you so much. - This is Paul Graves, purple state.
- 立场不明 - 就像巴克斯特
- He could go either way. - Like Baxter.
我不知道吉米·欧文斯为格雷福斯工作的啊
I didn't know Jim Owens was working for Graves.
对 噢 那不是你的工作伙伴吗
Yeah. Oh, man, that was your one work friend.
对 他在被总统炒了之后就不接我电话了
Yeah, he wouldn't return my calls after POTUS fired him.
都这么久了 去和他聊聊
Oh, come on. It's been a long time. Go talk to him.
- 我不行 - 迈克
- I can't. I can't. - Mike.
总统女士 每个人都知道我不喜欢奥布莱恩
Madam President, everyone knows I'm no fan of O'Brien,
但如果我要跨过党派
but if I'm gonna cross party
助你成为总统
lines in order to hand you the presidency,
我需要一些大礼
I'm gonna need something big.
好的 多大?
Okay, how big?
国务卿怎么样?
Why don't we go with Secretary of State?
至少我们知道你不需要大蛋蛋
Well, at least we know you don't need big balls.
- 绝对够大 - 对吧?
- Got large stones for sure. - Right?
我觉得这件事
I think it's something
可能可以达成一致
we might be able to accommodate.
- 好极了 那么 总统女士... - 嗯?
- Excellent. Then, Madam President... - Yes?
- ...你获得了我的支持  - 这就是我想听到的
- ...you have my support. - Oh, that's what I wanted to hear.
十分感谢 议员
Thank you so much, Congressman.
享受聚会 好吗? 开心
Hey, enjoy the party, okay? Have fun.
我们拿下格雷福斯了
Ooh, we got Graves.
- 真是棒极了 - 就是
- That was fantastic. - I know it.
等等 那道尔怎么办? 你答应过他让他当国务卿的
Oh, what about Doyle? You promised him State.
- 他知道我肯定会食言的 - 现在应该让他知道了
- He knows I don't keep my promises. - He should know by now.
我爱死你的选区了
Oh, I love your district.
我也爱你的选区
And I love your district.
两个我都爱
I love them both.
- 嘿 你去哪了？ - 怎么了？
- Hey, where have you been? - What?
尼克尔森看来要背叛咱了
Turns out Nickerson is back on the fence.
她说她从来没完全同意过要公开支持你
She said she never fully agreed to endorse you or support you.
- 她说过 - 然后我说要是我从你的耳朵进去操你脑子
- She did. - And I said maybe you'd remember
你恐怕会记得清楚点
better if I fuck your brain through your ear hole.
然后她怎么说 威尔？
Then what did she say, Will?
他对你火冒三丈 先生
She's pretty furious about it, sir.
- 本 你得去 - 交给我吧
- Ben, you got to - I'm on it.
汤姆为什么在那和耶格聊天
Why is Tom over there chatting it up with Jaeger?
- 不知道 我过去看看 - 不用 不用
- I don't know. I'll handle it. - No, no.
不劳您在这展现您不露声色的小魅力了
I don't need your subtle charm on this.
比尔 你好啊
Bill, hi.
我只是想再次确认下你说过会支持我 这话还算数吧
Just wanted to reconfirm that I can still count on your vote.
实际上 总统女士
Actually, Madam President,
我最近认真地拷问了一下自己的灵魂
I've been doing quite a bit of soul searching
恐怕我要听从我的良心了
and I'm afraid I need to listen to my conscience.
良心? 你他娘的在说些啥子?
Conscience? What the fuck are you talking about?
在我虔诚地思考后 我决定在接下来的
After much prayerful consideration, I have decided to abstain
国会决胜投票中弃权
from the upcoming congressional tie-breaking vote in Congress.
- 弃权? - 是的 总统女士
- Abstain? - Yes, ma'am.
那就没人赢了 你个蠢蛋
But then no one wins, you dumbass.
有人已经提醒过我你会说些伤人的话的
I was warned that you would say some hurtful things.
好吧 等等 我试试这么说
Okay, hold on. Let me see if I can just explain this to you
看你能不能懂
in terms that you might understand, okay?
设想啊 你的办公室主任娜迪亚 对吗?
Let's say that your chief of staff, Nadia, is it?
- 这 - 她跪在你面前
- That’s - Okay, and she's down on her knees
手里捧着你的蛋
and she's got your balls in her hand
用你最爽的方式抚慰着你的弟弟
and she's working your shaft just the way you like it.
然后就在你高潮要来
And moments before you're about to come
准别射那斯拉夫傻妞一脸的前一刻
all over her stupid Slavic face,
她说 "不不 经过我虔诚的思考
she says, "Nyet, after much prayerful consideration,
我决定在接下来的舔弟弟环节中弃权"
I have to abstain from the upcoming blowjob."
这个比方里 你是娜迪亚吧?
Are you Nadia in this situation?
给我有多远滚多远 妈的
Just get out of my sight. Oh, God, fuck.
- 好了 - 让我猜一下 耶格弃权了
- Okay. - Let me guess, Jaeger's abstaining.
- 是 - 尼克尔森也弃了
- Yeah. - Nickerson, too.
汤姆并没有帮奥布莱恩拉票
Tom's not lobbying votes for O'Brien.
他是在劝人们弃权
He's asking people to abstain.
这他妈到底怎么回事？
What the fuck is happening?
如果没人能在众议院拿到多数票
If no one gets a majority in the House,
就要到参议院投票表决 大选夜的时候我就解释过了
the vote goes to the Senate. I explained this on election night.
- 我当时没听 - 你是没听 但很明显汤姆听了
- I wasn't listening. - Yeah, but obviously Tom was.
汤姆·詹姆斯是公认的
Tom James is an acknowledged
掌握参议院规则和程序的行家
master of the Senate's rules and procedures.
如果到了参议院表决 汤姆就下一任总统了
So if it's up to the Senate, Tom is our next president.
那就必须得阻止他了
Well, he must be stopped.
现在把道尔拉回来还来得及吗
Is it too late to get Doyle back?
- 我们今晚忘了邀请他了 - 好样的
- We forgot to invite him tonight. - Okay.
- 真棒 - 汤姆!
- That's great. - Tom!
- 女士 - 格里芬议员 格里芬太太 你好吗汤姆
- Ma'am. - Congressman Griffin. Mrs. Griffin. How are you?
- 我很好 谢谢你 女士 - 那就好
- I'm very well, thank you, ma'am. - Good.
我整晚都在观察你 我知道你在打什么算盘
I've been watching you all night and I know what you're up to.
你在努力鼓足勇气邀请我与你共舞?
You're trying to get up the courage to ask me to dance.
我招供
Guilty.
女士 与您共舞 荣幸之至
Ma'am, I would be honored.
谢谢你的邀请
Oh, thank you.
谢谢你
Thank you. Hey.
- 你好 - 他邀请我的
- How are you? - He asked.
- 谢谢 谢谢 - 是他邀请我跳的
- Thank you. Thank you. - He asked me.
今晚各种见面 打招呼 寒暄
I think all this meeting and
真是累得我食欲大开啊
greeting has really made me work up an appetite.
- 我要饿死了 - 没错
- I'm starving. - Yeah,
你可是从没机会在这种场合吃东西呢
you never get the chance to eat at these things.
从来没有 你知道我最想吃什么吗
Never. You know what I really have a hankering for?
- 啥? - 韩国烤肉
- What's that? - Korean barbecue.
- 你喜欢韩国烤肉吗 - 还可以
- Do you like Korean barbecue? - It's okay.
我知道有一家很好吃的店
There's this great place that I heard about.
在安嫩代尔 叫啥名儿来着
It's in Annandale. What is the name of it?
让我好好想想
I'm trying to remember.
哦 对了 没错 叫
Oh, right, right. Um...
舔屌叛徒
the Cocksucking Backstabber.
来 接着跳啊 汤姆 别停啊
Oh, keep dancing, Tom. Don't stop dancing.
别到处看了 没人会帮你的
Don't look around. Nobody's gonna help you.
不 别这样 女士 请让我解释一下
No, no. Right. Ma'am, let me explain.
我想 你说的是
What what what that I think you're referring
我想咱还是找个安静的地方私下谈谈吧
You know what? I think maybe we should go and talk in private.
时机刚好 不是吗
That's perfect timing, isn't it? Yeah?
没错
Yes.
- 谢谢你的支持 - 谢谢
- Thank you for your support. - Thank you.
- 谢谢大家 - 非常感谢
- Thank you all. - Thank you so much.
- 很高兴见到大家 - 过来 别想跑
- So nice to see you all. - Come. You can't get away.
- 我们走吧 - 好吧
- Let's go. Yeah. - Okay. All right.
- 没错 我们要说清楚的 - 谢谢
- Right, we're gonna do it. - Thank you.
你怎么这么蠢 你个狗娘养的阴险小人
How stupid are you, you motherfucking snake?
你跟马伍德和珀塞尔见面的事儿我知道的一清二楚
I know all about your meeting with Marwood and Purcell.
我还知道你想用你
I know all about how you're trying to fuck me
那套弃权计划搞垮我
with that abstinence program of yours.
在你这看似光彩
Underneath this whole honorable,
体面 像童子军一样健康的外表下
decent, wholesome Boy Scout crap of yours,
我看得清楚你到底是个啥货色
I know exactly who you are.
- 你知道? - 是的 我当然知道
- Oh, you do? - Yes, I do.
好 所以我不用告诉你
Right, so I don't have to explain
我不是一个会把总统之位
that I am not someone who would piss away my presidency
- 浪费在做一堆操蛋决定上的人 - 啥？
- on a bunch of half-ass decisions. - What?
另外 也绝不会用来操
And, by the way, by messing around with that pretty boy
小美男子查理·贝尔德
Charlie Baird, for God's sake.
查理·贝尔德?
What? Charlie Baird?
关他啥事?
What does Charlie Baird have to do with any of this?
我也不知道 不关他的事
I don't know. He's got nothing to do with it.
- 天哪 你满嘴胡话! - 重点是...
- Oh, my God, you're such a liar! - The point is he...
你就编吧你!
You're such a liar!
那你一开始为什么要答应做副总统?
Why did you even join my ticket in the first place?
因为相信为人民服务是正确的
Because I happen to believe in something called public service.
- 放屁! - 那我他妈的也不知道为啥
- Oh, bullshit! - Okay, well, then I got no fucking idea.
- 老娘来告诉你 - 说吧
- I'll tell you why. - Go ahead.
因为你想离总统之位进一步
Because you wanted to be a step closer to the presidency
离我进一步
and to me.
- 呵呵哒 - 你想得不得了 看你的饥渴样
- Oh, my God. - You wanted it so bad, you could taste it.
难以置信 得了吧
This is unbelievable. Please.
你又在撒谎了
You are lying now just like you lied back then
就像之前你撒谎说
just like you lied about
不记得那晚发生在出租车上的事了
that night in the cab with the green shoes.
我简直不知道你在说什么
Oh, well, now I got no idea what you're talking about.
- 呵呵 你懂的 - 我不懂
- Yeah, you know exactly what I'm talking about. - No.
你记得那晚的绿鞋子
You remembered the green shoes that night,
却不记得你想要操我?
but not the fact that you wanted to fuck me?
得了吧
Come on. Come on.
直男是不可能记住女生穿的什么鞋的
No straight man remembers a woman's shoes.
得 我承认 我是基佬…
Well, you got me. I'm gay, so...
承认吧 你敢不敢说一次真话?
Just admit it. Just say the truth for once in your life.
汤姆 你那晚就是想操我
Come on, Tom. You wanted to fuck me that night.
- 承认吧你 - 别说了?!
- Just say it. - Will you stop it?!
说吧 说你想干死我
Just say it. You wanted to fuck my brains out.
好吧 我就是想干死你!
All right, I wanted to fuck your brains out!
我就知道 今晚你又想方设法搞我
There you go. And now you're trying to fuck me tonight.
- 错了 我今晚就是要搞你 - 我才要搞你
- No, I am fucking you tonight. - I'm gonna fuck you.
辞职对我来说还言之过早呢
I mean, if I never see the White House again, it'll be too soon.
可笑的是 我热爱我的工作
It's funny, you know. I love my job.
我从15议员岁起就在为弗朗工作了
I've been working for Congressman Furlong since I was 15.
迈克 总统在哪?
Mike, where's the president?
- 还有汤姆在哪? - 我不知道
- And where's Tom? - I don't know.
- 你醉了? - 你猜呀 酒鬼先生
- What, are you drunk? - Maybe, Mr. Hipflask.
老子醉了也能工作
Listen, I'm a high functioning alcoholic
你就是个烂酒鬼 快点去做事
and you're a sloppy weekend drunk. Now get with it.
总统女士 你在吗?
Ma'am?
嗨 我是乔纳·瑞安 今晚很高兴见到你
Hi. Jonah Ryan. Thanks for coming out tonight.
瑞安竞选活动
卡尔顿保龄球场
有问题尽管来找我 嗨 我是乔纳·瑞安
Let me know if you have any questions. Hi. Jonah Ryan.
我在竞选议员 希望你们能支持我
Running for Congress and I hope I can count on your support.
这位是我老板波莉 今晚她带我
This is my boss Polly. She's gonna be showing me the ropes today.
波莉 看这个
Oh, Polly, look at this.
大鞋子 这说明什么呢?
Big shoes. You know what that means, right?
大脚丫子?
Uh, big feet?
一针见血啊 你才应该去竞选议员呢
Can't argue with that. Maybe you should run for Congress.
- 你叫乔纳? - 是啊
- Your name is Jonah, right? - Yeah.
那你衣服为什么写的乔内·H·瑞安?
So why does your shirt say Jon H Ryan?
我草
Fuck.
今晚进展不错
This is good. This is working.
在保龄球馆拉票从来都不会错
Oh, bowling alley's always a good choice.
对男候选人来说 滑冰场虽说也是个好选择
I mean, skating rink's good for a male candidate,
但太冷了 都没啥妹子
but it's cold and gals tend to nip out.
- 嗨 我是乔... - 嗨 乔纳
- Hi, I'm Jo... - Hey, Jonah.
麻烦给我双12码的童鞋
Could I get a child size 12, please?
你在这干嘛 泰迪
What are you doing here, Teddy?
我来打保龄球啊
I'm looking forward to some bowling.
不过我更喜欢口袋台球呢[隔衣袋手淫]
Although pocket pool is more my game.
死变态 你听着
You listen to me, you fucking weirdo.
我是被你伤害了 但我不会让你定义我
I was a victim, but I am not gonna let you define me.
好演讲啊小妞
Nice blog, Mary.
告诉你 你这种人
You know what? People like you,
虽然有着人的外表 但却是不完整的
you look like us, but there's a little piece missing.
你就是个畜生
You're like a different species
老天爷自会惩罚你
and one that I hope gets struck from the Earth
你是恶霸 而我 乔纳·瑞安 不会向恶霸低头
because you're a bully and Jonah Ryan stands up to bullies.
乔纳· 瑞安威武
Yes. Yes, he does
谢谢大家 滚吧 这不是你们这些畜生该呆的地方
Thank you. Yeah. Yeah, this is a no haters alley.
好了 你和卵蛋爱抚男
Okay, you and Boo-Boo the ball-fondling bear here
快他妈滚出去
have exactly two seconds to get the fuck out.
我们这就走 跟塞琳娜问个好
Our work is done here. Tell Selina hello.
丹 这地方选的不错啊
Yeah, great place for an event, Dan.
厕所贩毒的小屁孩儿们也觉得这地方不错呢
The teenager selling cocaine in the bathroom thought so, too.
你蛋蛋不错嘛 年轻人
Oh, looking good, 26.
白宫东厅
总统女士 您看见汤姆了吗?
Ma'am, have you seen Tom?
- 看见好几次了 - 好的
- Couple times. - Good.
我们要搞定尼克森和耶格
I need Nickerson, I need Jaeger,
我们要赢
cause we're gonna finish this.
好的 跟我来
Okay, walk this way.
抓住你了!
Gotcha!
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
我能跟你去绿厅说几句话吗?
Can I have a few minutes of your time in the Green Room?
绿厅啊? 看来很有历史意义啊
The Green Room? That sounds historic.
必须的 伍德罗·威尔逊
Oh, it is. It's where Woodrow Wilson
在那中风过好几次呢
had some of his most significant strokes.
- 讲真? - 真的
- Really? - Yeah.
- 嗨 兄弟 好久不见 - 迈克
- Hey, buddy. Been a while. - Mike.
真是对不起啊 事情搞砸了
Look, about how things went down at the end, I am so sorry.
我应该谢谢你的 这件事给我敲醒了我
I should thank you, cause it was a wake-up call
让我远离疯狂的特区政治
for me to get out of the insanity of DC politics.
那不错啊 兄弟 这地方糟透了
Amen to that, brother. This place sucks.
我找到了个超棒的私人机构的工作
Listen, I have lined up a sweet private sector gig.
悄悄跟你说 我也找到了个工作
Oh? On the QT, I got something in the works, too.
我现在是全国曲棍球联合会的通讯部主管
I am the new director of communications for the NHL.
- 你得到了那工作啊 真好 - 你呢?
- You got the hockey job. Perfect. - Where are you headed?
我要去CL国际时事上班
I'm going to CL International Time.
- 听起来不错啊 - 是的 大公司呢
- That sounds great. - Mmm, big.
兄弟 啥时候需要球赛门票
Listen, any time you want Caps tickets,
就来找我哈
you hit me up, buddy, all right?
你要是需要啥国际的东西来找我
And if you ever need anything international.
- 恭喜 - 同喜
- And congratulations. - You, too.
- 祝你好运 - 你也是
- Mazel. Yeah. - Good luck.
混蛋
Fuck.
如果你认为你现在快要
If you think that you are getting
拿到那些一文不值的玩具船
those worthless toy boats now,
那我就要在你在T恤衫上贴钻之前
I'm gonna shut down those factories
关掉那些工厂
faster than you can bedazzle a fucking sweatshirt.
- 废话少说 赛琳娜 - 这就对了
- Let's cut the shit, Selina. - Oh, here it is.
我管着科罗拉多州所有路
All roads through Colorado go through me
通行费刚上涨
and the toll just went up.
你这是玩斗鸡游戏 而且你还是该死的打头阵的母鸡
You're playing a very dangerous game of chicken
这非常危险
with the head fucking hen.
因为如果我没有赢得选举
Cause if I don't win the White House,
奥布莱恩就会把你的破船变成沉船
O'Brien is gonna sink your stupid boats
然后你就会穿着90年代的新娘礼服
and you're gonna look like a hair-sprayed asshole
看起来像一只长满毛的肛门
in your 1980s mother-of-the-bride dress.
如果我赢了 我就让自己的部门
And if I do win, I will have my administration
到你的屎一样的破烂地方去
come to your shitty little district
像弄死危地马拉的保姆一样弄死你们
and shake it to death like a Guatemalan nanny.
然后我会让美国国家税务局
And then I'm gonna have the IRS crawl so far up
深深地爬到你丈夫的肠子里
your husband's colon, he's gonna wish
他得期待他们只找到更多癌细胞
the only thing they find is more cancer.
我的天
Good God.
所以 我能期待你的选票吗？
So can I count on your vote?
或者说我要在你那松弛的 生过六个孩子的阴道里
Or do I need to shove a box of White House M&Ms
塞一盒白宫的M&M豆?
up your stretched-out, six-baby vag?
好 我投给你
Yes, you can count on my vote.
我觉得我更想听到你说
I think I want to hear
某问题啦票票来啦
an okey-dokey, Annie Oakley.
Okey-dokey, Annie Oakley.
非常好
Oh, super-duper, trooper.
现滚出去吧 议员女士
Now get the fuck out of here, Congresswoman.
艾米 圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas, Amy.
你是凯蒂·卡罗索
Oh, Candi Caruso is who you are.
我很惊讶在内华达事件之后在这里看见你
I'm surprised to see you here after what happened in Nevada.
"内-华-达" 我告诉总统有个更适合
"Nev-add-a." I told POTUS that there are other qualified people
特别顾问的人选
out there for special advisor,
但是她坚持没有了 所以...
but she insisted she couldn't think of any, so...
猜发生了什么
Oh. Guess what.
我订婚了
I am engaged.
谁... 和谁订婚？
Who's... who... to whom?
盖瑞·威尔什
Gary Welsh. You know, Gary Welsh.
- 盖瑞·威尔什？- 州议员盖瑞·威尔什
- Gary Welsh? - Gary Welsh at State.
他本应该是最性感的50员工表单上的
He was supposed to be on this 50 Hottest thing that I'm in,
但是他们把他的名字弄错了 他们拼错了
but they got his name wrong. They spelled it incorrectly.
结果真的有另外一个人叫那个名字
Turns out there's an actual guy by that name.
他们就让那个人当选了
They put him in instead.
- 那真是糟糕 - 非常糟糕
- That's just a bad thing. - Terrible. Terrible.
我很遗憾 但是你订婚我很高兴
I'm sorry to hear that, but happy for you.
- 谢谢 - 那么
- Oh! Thank you. - All that.
总统在呼唤我
President of the United States needs me.
- 所以... - 请便
- So... - Mmm, yeah.
保重
Take care.
- 奥佩 拿上你的浣熊皮帽子 我们走 - 好的
- Hey, Opie, grab your coonskin cap and let's get out of here. - Oh, okay.
- 不是你 - 什么?
- It wasn't you. - What?
你一点都不性感 州议员盖瑞·威尔什才是 你是因为印刷错误才当选的
You're not hot. Gary Welsh at State is. You're a typo.
但是 正如你所说的 这跟头脑无关 而是与内心有关
But like you said, it's not up here, it's what's in here.
- 带我向您的夫人问好 - 好的 女士
- And won't you give my regards to your wife? - Yes, ma'am.
她是威斯康辛州红十字会的负责人 你知道么?
She's the head of the Red Cross in Racine, did you know that?
- 她是一个圣人 - 我会投您一票的，总统女士
- She's a saint. - You can count on my vote, Madam President.
- 这是你的承诺 - 是的 是承诺
- That is a promise. - Oh, yes, it is a promise.
走吧 转身 走
Yes. Go. Turn, go.
我觉得这个聚会
Well, ah, I guess this party
正式结束了 情况如何
is officially now over. So how did we do?
和舞会刚开始时候差不多
We're about the same place we
多了格拉夫的票
were at the beginning of the ball plus Graves.
我们应该能拿到普拉特的选票
We could have secured Platt,
但是他没拿到那张有他夫人设计的包包的照片
but he never got the picture with his wife's purse.
我只希望新罕布什尔州一切顺利
I just hope things are going good in New Hampshire.
晚上好 首先我们要展示一些有关国会议员约翰·赖安
Good evening. We begin with some shocking footage
的一些令人震惊的画面
of congressional candidate Jonah Ryan
均由非专业录音机捕获
all captured on amateur video.
我们要提醒各位
We do have to warn you, though,
瑞安的语言十分粗鲁直接
Ryan's language is extremely graphic.
你这种人 虽然有着人的外表
People like you, you look like us,
但却是不完整的
but there's a little piece missing.
你就是个畜生
You're a different species,
老天爷自会惩罚你
one that I hope gets struck from the Earth.
我去
Fuck me, Amadeus.
我们都看不见乔纳在吼谁
Can't even see the guy that Jonah's yelling at.
天哪 波莉不会认为我在吼她吧？
God, Polly's not gonna think that I was yelling at her, will she?
我们为什么不打电话给她的宣传人员问问呢?
Why don't we call her publicist and find out?
等等 理查德
Wait a second. Richard,
你一定有从另一个角度拍摄的视频吧
tell me you have that from the other angle.
当然
Oh, definitely.
乔纳 我要一个儿童款12码的
Hey, Jonah. I'll get a child size 12, please.
你在那干什么
What are you doing here?
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
我不知道发生了什么
I don't know what happened there.
- 你又他妈搞砸了 - 一模一样的混蛋事
- You did the same fucking thing! - Literally.
你知道么
Oh, yeah, you know what?
你是对的 确实是一模一样的
You're right, I did the exact same thing.
大选之后
After the national elections,
总统经历了一些困难
the president may have found herself with a bad lie in the rough,
但是待经济稳定之后
but after stabilizing the economy,
众议院投票就开始像打高尔夫球
the House vote is starting to look like a gimme putt.
记住我的话 总统将最终拔得头筹
And mark my words, the president will end up atop the leaderboard
就像朴英碧和高宝璟
just like Inbee Park or Lydia Ko
或者其他美国女子职业高尔夫巡回赛中
or any of the other great female golfers
优秀的高尔夫球女选手
in the LPGA Tour.
我想回到
I would like to get back to questions
总统女儿的同性恋问题
about the first daughter's lesbianism.